Because my legs are full.
足がいっぱいしてるからね
Okay, do you want to go see the pizza party?
よし、ピザパーティーは見に行きますか?
Serve me a drink...
飲み物を出して...
It smells really good.
めっちゃいい匂いするんやけん
It smelled like it was quite crowded.
結構混んでたような匂い
Today is Friday Flower Gold.
今日は金曜花金です
It's just deep.
深いだけやな
With spirit.
気合いで
Do you want to put ice?
氷入れる?
Yeah.
うん
I haven't been able to break my face lately.
最近自分の顔面折れないんで
Have black hair.
黒髪にして
cute?
可愛い?
It's still cute.
可愛いには変わりない
Is it true?
本当かい?
Yeah.
うん
Heavy!
重 っ!
This is terrible!
やばいぞ!
It's Broomy.
ブリューミーだね
I did it
やった
ー.
ー
It wasn't there before.
この 前はなかったのに
That's right.
そうよ
I chinked it.
チンクしたの
Well then.
じゃーん
I got sick.
病気になりました
Some of them are some of them.
ある中ある中ある中
Leave this.
これ置いて
leave.
置 いて
oh
お
- Looks delicious.
ー うまそう
That's amazing.
す げーじゃん
Well then.
じゃーん
Pizza.
ピザー
Is this fried chicken?
これ唐揚げかな?
Yeah.
うん
Should I put a fork or something?
フ ォークか何か入れる?
Yeah.
うん
Let's get it out just in case.
一応出しとこう
It's hot.
あっつい
It's freshly made.
できたてだもん
Let's have a toast.
乾杯しましょう
cheers.
乾杯
The pizza looks really good.
ピザまじうまそうやん
Looks delicious.
おいしそう
I forgot what it was.
何が何だか忘れちゃった
I wonder where Milfino is.
どこはミルフィーノなんだろうね
You might find out by eating it.
食ってみて分かるかも
surely.
確かに
cheers.
乾杯
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ
This is shrimp, right?
これシュリンプでしょ
What is shrimp?
シュリンプは何?
I wonder if this is shrimp shrimp.
これエビシュリンプじゃないかな
This looks like a bed color.
これね、なんかおねつきカラーみたいな
You can eat it.
食べてもいいからね
Really?
本当に?
never mind.
気にしないで
I'll have the maid come later.
後でね、メイド来てもらうけど
You don't have to worry about that.
そんなのは気にしなくていいよ
Is the maid coming?
メイド来ちゃう?
Well, that's what I need to see.
やっぱ、見てもらわないとさ、そこが
So that you can't see the cosplays in the store.
店のコスプレを見れないように
Well then, let's go.
じゃあ、行っちゃう
Where should I start?
何から行こうかな
Makes me want to sit down.
下に座りたくなるね
Shall we sit downstairs?
下に座ろうかな
Me, then this.
俺、じゃあこれ
nice.
いいね
But after all, it has thick Milfino in it.
でもやっぱね、分厚いミルフィーノが入ってるだけあって
Then this.
じゃあ これ
Just a little, the cheese will probably stick to you,
ちょっとね、多分チーズくっついちゃうから、
I think I'll leave it a little farther away.
若干こう離しておこうかな
Please eat.
食べてください
I'll enjoy having this.
いただ きます
delicious.
おいしい
Oh no.
やば
delicious.
おいしい
It's been a while since I ate pizza, but it was delicious.
久しぶりにピザ食べたけど、おいしいわ
Now that's super cheesy.
もうさ、超チーズだね
It certainly feels like that.
確かに、そういうことかって感じ
I see.
なるほどね
It's so delicious.
めっちゃおいしい
It's like eating cheese.
チーズ食べてるみたい
Too cheesy.
チーズすぎて
It definitely tastes like Christmas.
確かにクリスマスって感じの味
This makes me quite hungry.
これはね、結構お腹溜まるね
It accumulates in my stomach.
お腹に溜まる
This is coming.
来るね、これは
Lunch?
お昼ご飯?
Eat both lunch and dinner.
お昼と夜、両方食べる
Both are OK.
両方OKだね
It's early if you come at night.
夜に来たら早い
It's so delicious.
うますぎ
Even if you still eat at the same time.
同じ時間でもまだ食べても
If you exercise, you'll be fine.
運動すれば平気だ
Good thing.
いいこと
So cute.
可愛いやっぱ
TRUE?
本当?
Yay, good.
やった、よかった
I'm really happy.
本当嬉しい
Cute, my favorite.
可愛い、お気に入り
Is this only gray?
これはさ、色グレーだけ?
There was also this color.
なんかね、この色もあった
But this one suited me best.
けど、これが一番似合ってた
I don't really have these two roles.
なかなかこの二役いないよ
Really?
本当に?
I'm happy again.
また嬉しい
cute.
可愛い
good.
よかった
From the moment I saw the photo, I thought it was cute.
写真見せてもらった時から、これ可愛いと思ったよ
It's like light blue, it's gray.
水色っぽいね、グレーのね
It seems like a brevet.
ブルベらしい
Brevet.
ブルベね
Brevet color.
ブルベカラー
It's unnecessary because I have black hair, but it looks good.
黒髪にしたから余計ね、いい感じ
It's smooth.
サラサラよ
After all, she has black hair.
やっぱ黒髪よ
After all, only black hair can win.
や っぱ黒髪しか勝たん
It's totally fine, Chapa is strong.
全然いいもん、チャパ強い
TRUE?
本当?
I was told that I suddenly felt younger.
なんか、いきなり幼くなったねって言われた
No, I'll probably have it again.
いや、それで多分また持てちゃうよ
TRUE?
本当?
Can I have it?
持てるかな?
in trouble.
困る
I would be in trouble if I had it.
持てたら困ります
Be popular.
モテモテになって
I'm having trouble with the increase in customers.
お 客さん増えて困ります
Please don't have any more.
これ以上持てないでください
I can't have it.
持てません
You had a lot of them, even now.
いっぱい持ってたでしょ、今でも
Not at all.
全然だよ
TRUE?
本当?
I haven't had a boyfriend for about 3 years, and I haven't had a boyfriend for 2 or 3 years.
彼氏とか3年くらい、2、3年ちゃんといないもん
Really.
本当に
If that's not enough, why don't you like people?
あんまりじゃあ何、人好きにならないの?
I haven't had any encounters.
出会いがないの
No encounters?
出会いがない?
Yeah.
うん
Even if you go to Concafe, you won't meet anyone.
コ ンカフェやってても出会いがないか
Yes, I'll do Concafe, but
そう、コンカフェやってやるけど、
Are Concafe customers a good target?
コンカフェのお客さんは対象がいいの?
Yes, because the target is good,
そう、対象がいいってなってるから、
It's a secret.
秘密であって
Do it like this.
こうやってね
I had an encounter.
出会いがあった
Misa-chan, how old do you like men?
みさちゃんはさ、 何歳くらいの男の人が好きなの?
Early 20's or so.
20前半とかさ
But maybe it's possible to be 14 years old or something.
でも、14代とかでもいけるかも
Even though I'm 14, I still like it.
14代でも全然好き
He'll be around my dad's age.
パパくらいの年代になっちゃうじゃん
I like kind people.
優しい人が好きなの
A kind person, to be more specific,
優しい人ってさ、さ、 具体的に言うとさ、
So kind.
あのくらい優しい
You're kind.
優しいんだ
There are people out there who actually say they like Misa.
ちゃんとみさのことを好きで言ってくれる人がいるな
There's someone who doesn't do what Misa does.
みさのことをしてない人があって
Well then, I think it's better for you to properly say that things that are different are different.
じゃあ、ちゃんと違うことは違うって言ってくれる方がいいって
thing?
こと?
I'm not saying anything is fine,
なん でもいいよっていうわけじゃなく、
Once I realized that Misa was wrong,
ちゃんとみさが間違ってることを知ったら、
It's different.
違うと
Someone who wants to say it.
言ってほしい人が
It's crazy that he hasn't been around for three years.
3年もいないってやばいね
There aren't many.
なかなかいない
Hey.
ね え
I can't.
できない
But you confessed a lot, right?
でも、告白をいっぱいされたでしょ?
I've never been.
されたことない
It may have never happened to you in your life.
人生で一回もされたことないかも
there were.
あった
Seriously.
マジ
Well then, Misa-chan, if you fall in love with me, it's fine.
じゃあ、みさちゃんはさ、好きになったら結構、
Are you the type who says it yourself?
自分から言っちゃうタイプ?
If you fall in love with it, you'll love it.
好きになったらめっちゃイチズ
lie?
うそ?
Yeah.
うん
I can't see it.
見えない
If you like it, Ichizu.
好きになったらイチズ
Huh.
へえ
Eat this?
これ食べて?
Let's eat.
食べよう
Well, now that he has a boyfriend...
じゃあ彼の、あれだ、彼氏ができたらもう、
Because all I can see is my boyfriend.
彼氏しか見えないから
Yes, one boyfriend.
そう、彼氏ひとすり
I don't care about other people.
他の人はどうでもいいからね
Well then, you can't do it.
じゃあ、できちゃダメだね
I won't be able to go to work.
仕事も行けなくなっちゃう
No, no.
ダメだ、ダメだ
This is no good because we won't be able to see each other again.
これはもう会えなくなっちゃうからダメだ
I won't be able to do it.
できなくなっちゃう
So, tell your boyfriend, for example, right now, this cafe.
じゃあ彼氏に例えば今さ、このカフェ、
If you tell me to quit my job, I'll quit.
仕事やめてって言われたらもうやめちゃう
I'll stop.
やめちゃう
You can't do that.
それはできちゃダメだ
in trouble.
困る
I won't be able to see you.
会えなくなる
Yes, that's why.
そう、だからね
I'd say it's really cool.
めっちゃイチズっていうかなっていうか
Well then, how many people have you dated?
じゃあさ、付き合った人数とかさ、
How many years have you been dating?
何年ぐらい付き合ってたとかさ、どんぐらいなの?
How many people have you dated so far?
何人と今までいたら付き合った?
If we started dating, it would be about two people.
付き合ったら2人ぐらい
2 people?
2人?
What year is the longest?
何年が一番長い?
2 and a half years.
2年半
It's long.
長いわ
I was alone for two and a half years.
2年半一人いた
Also, which one is the shortest?
あとはじゃあ一番短いのは?
3 months?
3ヶ月とか?
But it will be there for 3 months.
でも3ヶ月はいるんだじゃん
So how old is the oldest of the three?
じゃあその3人の中で一番年寄りは何歳ぐらい?
I was still young at that time.
まだその時は若かったからさ
26?
But it's amazing.
でもすごいね
26 is pretty high when you're a teenager.
10代の時に26って結構上だよね
I like older people.
年上の人が好き
Now I can go from 26 to 40.
今はもう26から40ぐらいまでいけるようになっちゃった
Broadly, yes.
幅広く、そう
You can fall in love with it.
好きになれる
She's a woman, she's an adult.
女性のね、大人だからね
You start to like older people.
年上の人好きになってくるんだよね
Yes, I like older people.
そう、年上の人が好き
Well, now it's starting to feel like it's impossible for someone my age.
じゃあもう今はさ、年近い子逆に無理みたいな感じになってきちゃ
cormorant?
う?
Maybe I don't like it that much.
なんか あんまり好きじゃないかもしれない
Will I no longer feel this attractive?
こう魅力的に感じなくなっちゃうのか
I think you're a kid.
ガキだなって思うじゃん
Well then, I'm starting to wonder if I really have to choose based on the face.
じゃあ 顔じゃほんと選ばないかなってきちゃう
But I can also see your face.
でも顔でも見ちゃう
What do you think?
どうでしょう?
Your face is also important.
顔も大事
Well, you said you're in your 40s now.
まあでも今の40代って言ったもんね、
Not so much yet.
まだそんなに
Yes, everyone is surprisingly young.
そう、意外とみんな若いからね
Everyone is working for the time being and using it to their advantage.
み んな一応気に使い勝ちで働けてるから
As long as we're together and walking next to each other, our faces are bound to deviate a little.
一緒一緒にいて、隣で歩く以上、やっぱ多少は顔面偏差ししちゃう
Right.
よね
For some reason, I wouldn't want my child to be born with a father-like personality.
何 か、いかにもパパみたいな感じで生まれたら嫌だもんね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I'd like to treat him as my boyfriend for the time being.
一応彼氏っていう部類で歩きたいもんね
If we're going to be together anyway, I want to be with my boyfriend.
どうせ一緒にいるんだったらね、彼氏ちゃんといたいし
I want to introduce it to my friends too.
友達にも紹介したいしね
I can properly introduce you to my boyfriend.
ちゃん と紹介できる、彼氏の
Let's drink, drink, drink.
飲んで飲んで、飲ましちゃおう
Drink after eating.
食べたら飲む
Eat and drink.
食べて飲む
But something popped out.
でもなんかぽっこり出して
It's because it's Ikatsuri.
いかつりだからそうだね
Let's pop out and wear cosplay.
ぽっこり出して、コスプレを着よう
Is it okay?
いいのかな?
I'm full.
お腹いっぱい
I can already see your beautiful waist.
綺麗なくびれはもう俺見てるからさ
I've already seen it at this cafe.
このカフェでもう見てるから
So, it's okay now.
だから もうね、別にいいよ
It's private today.
今日はプライベートだから
It's okay to have a chubby stomach.
お 腹 ぽっこりでもいい
I'd rather see a chubby belly.
むしろぽっこりのお腹を見たいよ
vice versa.
逆に
It's already out, though.
もう出てるよ、でも
Has it come out yet?
もう出た?
I usually have a really tight waist.
普段くびれすごいからさ
I feel like it's probably already out.
もう多分ね、出てる気がする
TRUE?
本当?
which one?
どれ?
Oh, amazing!
お、すごい!
She's already a pregnant woman.
もう妊婦さんじゃん
It's almost here already.
もう割と来てる
That's amazing.
すごいね
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
Is it okay?
いいの?
Isn't this what it's all about, as soon as you go to bed you're going to be in a heady state again?
これでもあれなの、寝たらすぐまたヘッコンじゃんでしょ?
I said, let's do something about it.
どうせいかすりましょうって
Yes, when I go to bed.
そう、寝たら
As soon as you go to bed or take it out.
寝たり、出したりしたらすぐ
That's amazing, that's good.
すごいね、いいじゃん
It becomes.
なっちゃう
Okay, okay, that's it.
いいよ、いいよ、それな
It's like waiting for a baby.
幼児待機みたいな
My stomach is bulging.
お腹ぽっこりして
It's okay if you move.
動けば大丈夫
Is it possible if I move?
動 けばいけるか
What is this?
これなんだろう?
Is it basil?
バジルかな?
Is this an avocado?
これはアボカド?
Isn't this asparato chicken?
これはアスパラトチキンじゃない?
I see.
なるほどね
No, there are quite a few things I don't like.
うそ、嫌いなの結構ある?
sweet.
甘い
Can you eat anything?
何でも食べれちゃう?
Avocado is sweet.
アボカドは甘い
Don't you like it?
好きじゃない?
rare.
珍しい
I have an image of girls liking avocados.
女 子アボカド好きなイメージはあるから
I didn't like sweets.
甘い好きじゃなかった
I tried eating it.
食べてみたら
What else?
他は?
With sea urchins.
ウニと
Sea urchin, you're eating too much.
ウニね、食べ過ぎだ
I've eaten too much.
食べ過ぎだ
It's good, that's it.
うまいよ、それね
Delicious shrimp.
美味しい、エビは
Yes, both the shrimp and scallops were delicious.
そう、エビもホタテも美味しかった
delicious.
美味しい
I was hooked.
ハマっちゃった
I bought it myself.
自分で買っちゃったもんね
How many days will it arrive?
何日届くんだろう?
Delivered within 1 day.
1日に届く
the day after tomorrow?
明後日?
It will arrive the day after tomorrow.
明後日届く
Matsumae pickles.
松前漬け
Kazunoko pickled in Matsumae.
松前漬けのカズノコ
I bought two packs.
ツーパック買ってた
Did you also buy a two-pack?
ツーパックも買ったの?
Yeah.
うん
It says 3500 yen.
3500円って書いてある
That's a pretty good price.
結構いい値段だね
Good price.
いい値段
So that's it, at home.
それであれだよ、家で
You can drink sake while eating Matsumae pickles.
松前漬け食いながら、酒いけるよ
I can have some sake.
酒いけるよ
I'll probably definitely go ahead with the meal.
多分絶対ご飯が進む
I thought I'd buy some food too.
ご飯もちゃんと買っとこうと思って
Chin's one.
チンのやつね
チ ンのやつ
Because I don't have a rice cooker at home.
お家に炊飯器ないから
real?
ほんと?
I can't make meals at home.
ご飯作れないからな、家では
I'll buy you a rice cooker.
炊飯器ぐらい買ってあげるよ
But it's easier to do it.
でもチンした方が楽だからね
After all, there's no need to cook strawberries if you have any left over.
結局苺炊くのもさ、余っちゃったりしたら
Soppabane.
そ っぱばね
It would be a waste if possible.
できればもったいない
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
One Chin one costs about 100 yen.
チンのやつ1個だって100円くらいでいってるもんね
Yeah yeah yeah.
うん うんうん
Drink, drink.
飲んで飲んで
Drink, drink, drink.
飲んで飲んで飲んで
Delicious.
う ま い
It's good and delicious.
うまいし、うまい
Because there's tequila loin.
テキラロースがあるんだから
I'm getting drunk, I'm getting drunk.
酔っ払っちゃう酔っ払っちゃう
I get drunk.
酔っ払っちゃう
I guess I'll leave this for a while.
これこの間のちょっと残れかな
Only a little.
ちょっとしかない
About a third left.
あと3分の1くらい
There's one more thing left.
あともう1個あるから
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
There's one more.
もう1個あるんですよ
There was absolutely nothing.
全然ありました
This smells like milk.
匂いはこれミルクなんだよね
Pretty strawberry milk.
結構苺ミルク
It looks super sweet though.
超甘そうに見えるんだけど
Tequila loin properly.
ちゃんとテキラロース
If you drink it.
飲むとね
Not quite full yet.
全然いっぱいまだ
Not many?
多くない?
I can have it again.
もう一度いただける
At Nanami.
なみなみで
Nanami tequila loin.
なみなみテキラロース
It smells amazing.
すごい匂いが
The smell of strawberries.
いちごの匂いが
I'm going to piss you off.
むかいざきしちゃう
It's Mukaiizaki.
むかいざきだ
If you eat it, you'll calm down a bit.
食べればまだね、ちょっと落ち着くよね
If I don't eat anything, I'll be like, "Wow."
何も食べないとさ、うーってなるけどさ
It's usually full inside.
だいたい中いっぱいになって
After all, cheese is heavy.
やっぱチーズが重いんだよ
Cheese might be heavy.
チーズ重いかも
Let's eat slowly.
ゆっくり食べよう
It's still early.
まだ時間も早い
What is this?
なにこれね、もうなんか
To that.
あれにと
With Nogidakani.
のぎだかにと
Oh, really?
うそー、本当?
Can Nogidaka be included?
のぎだか入れるかな?
I'll put Nogidaka in.
のぎだか入れるよ
It's very student-like.
めっちゃ生徒系じゃん
I wanted to be an idol.
アイドルになりたかった
No way.
うそー
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it too late now?
今からでも遅くないんじゃない?
absolute.
絶 対
Can I become one?
なれるかな?
Idols can't dance for some reason.
アイドル、なんかダンスできないから
After all, not everyone can dance, right?
ダンスはだってみんなできないんじゃない?
If everyone practices.
みんな練習すれば
So you can talk on TikTok, right?
だからティクトークできるでしょ?
I'm working hard on TikTok.
ティクトークがんばってる
I'll ask you to dance a little later on TikTok.
ティクトークちょっと後で踊ってもらうよ
Can you dance?
踊れるかな?
I wonder what it was, I just did it.
なんだっけ、さっきやってたじゃん
Really.
ほんとね
That's fine.
いいじゃん
That's it, has the choreography been decided yet?
あれってさ、それがさ、もうさ、振付決まってんの?
Do you remember all the established ones?
決まってるやつをみんな覚えてるの?
oh yeah.
そうそう
I remember each and every one of the difficult things.
難しいの覚えるの、いちいち
But it's amazing, I still remember it.
でもすごいじゃん、今も覚えたの
I remember this because it's been popular for a long time.
これはもうね、もうずっと前から流行ってたから覚えた
How many more can you make?
あと何個ぐらいできるの?
I don't remember it because it was too difficult.
あと難しすぎて覚えてないな
There are also many shorter versions.
短いバージョンもいろいろあるよね
If it's something simple, I can remember it right away.
簡単なやつだったらすぐ見れば覚えるけど
difficult.
難しい
Pretty much all men are myrcene.
男は結構みんなミルセンだからね
Because I'm almost doing it.
ほぼやってるからね
Okay, let's take a break.
いいよ、休憩しよう
I have a good stomach.
お腹いいね
Shall we try some fried chicken?
唐揚げも食べてみようか
Yeah, it's delicious.
うん、おいしいよ
It's already cold.
もう冷めた
Yeah, it's delicious.
うん、うまっ
The fried chicken is also delicious.
唐揚げもおいしい
It's true.
本当だ
It's crazy, it's coming out.
やばいよ、出てますね
That's amazing.
すごいね
It will come out.
出てくるし
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみてよ
It came out from the side.
横から出た
It kind of looks like that.
なんかあれみたい
Looks like a galconette.
ギャルソネみたい
lie?
嘘?
Even though it's thin.
細いのにさ
amazing.
すごい
Are you not tired at all?
これ全然疲れてない?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Even so, it comes out a little.
それ でも ちょっと出ちゃう
amazing.
すごい
Do you want to wear cosplay while taking a break?
休憩がてらにコスプレ着ちゃう?
Then.
そしたら
Shall I wear it?
着ちゃおうか
That's it, clothes.
あれだもんね、洋服ね
Isn't that right?
なんか そう、ないんじゃない?
surely.
確かに
What a cute guy.
可愛 い や つね
Because it comes out a little expensive.
ちょっと高いのが出てくるから
I think it definitely suits you.
絶対それも似合うと思う
Really?
本当に?
Jean.
ジャンって
ジャン
Appeal to Jean.
ジャンってアピールして
Yes, I'll change my clothes.
はい、着替えまーす
I'll change my clothes.
着替えまーす
I'm a maid.
メイドでーす
This wall classic maid.
この壁定番のメイド
I'll wear it as a maid.
メイドちゃんで着ちゃいます
Change clothes.
着 替 え
This is cute, isn't it?
可愛いよね、これね
When it comes to maids, there are quite a lot of black ones.
メイドしたら結構黒が多いけどさ
If it's too dark.
あんまり黒くろしてると
surely.
確かに
It's not cute, it's a little whitish.
可愛くないから、ちょっと白っぽいやつ
It's so cute.
め っちゃ 可愛い
The whitish color is youthful, or rather pure.
白っぽいのが青春っていうか純粋っぽいじゃん
But there are many cute ones, like this one.
でも結構可愛いの多いよね、これね
There are so many cute things to do in cosplay.
コスプレにも可愛いのいっぱいあるからね
It's high quality.
クオリティ高いよね
The quality is too high.
クオリティ高すぎる
I'm wearing it while looking at it.
見ながら着てますよ
Yeah.
うん
Is everything included?
全部入ってる?
It's all included.
全部入ってます
probably.
おそらく
Shall I change my clothes?
生着替えしちゃいますか?
生着替えしちゃいますか
Fresh clothes.
生着替え
Then you can see what looks like a stomach.
そしたらちょうどお腹っぽいところ見れるし
Will I be seen?
見られちゃうの?
You can see it, Misa-chan.
見られちゃいますよ、みさちゃん
You can see me change my clothes.
生 着替え見られちゃいますよ
You'll be seen.
見られちゃいますよ
Make today look special.
今日は特別に見せてください
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
There are so many, I don't know which one to wear.
すごいいっぱいあって、どっち着ればいいのか分かんないわ
First of all, don't you want to wear it because it's big?
まず、大きいのから着ていきたいんじゃない?
It's the foundation.
土台だよね
Foundation.
土台
One piece base.
ワンピースの土台
I have to take my clothes off first.
まずは自分が脱がなきゃいけない
That's right.
そうだ
Start with yourself.
まずは自分から
nice.
いいね
Good.
よいしょ
oh!
おー!
These are super cute underwear.
すごいかわいい下着だ
I thought my stomach would be more visible, but it wasn't at all.
お腹、もっと出てると思ったら全然だった
Surprisingly.
意外と
Yes, my hair is a mess.
そう、髪の毛ボサボサだ
It's really late.
やっぱ遅いなぁ
It's amazing how hungry you are after eating.
食べてこのお腹だもんね、すごいよね
My hair is messy.
髪の毛ボサボサ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'll trade in my hair and underwear.
髪から下取っとくよ、下着
Cute underwear.
かわいい下着
TRUE?
本当?
What's going on behind that?
後ろどうなってんの、それ
It's cute.
かわいいじゃん
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
It feels good, it feels good.
いい感じよ、いい感じよ
cute?
かわいい?
It's the best.
最高よ
Okay, it's cold, so let's get changed.
いいよ、寒いからね、着替えちゃおうか、
Well then.
じゃあ
Let's wear it like this.
着ちゃおうか、このまま
Beautiful legs.
足、綺麗
Shall I wear it?
着ちゃおうか
I wonder what kind of underwear this is, I wonder if it's better to wear it.
これ下着はどうなんだろう、付けといた方がいいのかなぁ
Don't need it?
いらない?
Is that underwear too?
下着もあれか
I see, can you see the string?
そっか、紐が見えちゃうのか
Just once, let's take it.
一回じゃあ、取っちゃおうか
It's okay to take it.
取っちゃうの、いいじゃん
Okay, show me.
いいの、見せてくれ
特別
My shape is so good that I don't even need a bra.
なんか、ブラジャーいらないくらい形が整ってるね
TRUE?
本当?
It's difficult.
難しいなぁ
Okay.
よ い しょ
If you think it's just the top, please take off the bottom as well.
上だけかと思ったら、下も脱んでくれ
That's right, I forgot.
そうだった、忘れちゃった
Okay, okay, you can take your clothes off now.
いいよ、いいよ、もう脱いじゃっていいよ
That's it, you're already drunk.
あれだな、さてはもう酔っぱらってるな
I'm a little drunk.
ちょっと酔っぱらっちゃってる
I'll wear this.
これを着ます
Piper girl.
パ イパー女子
It's official.
オフィシャルですね
That's amazing.
すごいね
The skirt is so fluffy.
ふわっとなってるね、スカートね
It's true, for sure.
本当だね、確かに
cute.
かわいい
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Is this the waist?
これはウエストかな?
Ah, like this.
あ、こうか
Should I wear it from above?
上から着るのかな?
I see, at the waist.
なるほどね、ウエストのところに
Put it on.
つけて
It has a zipper.
チャックがついてる
Oh, that's true.
あ、ほんとだ
Does it feel like rolling?
巻く感じか
It's elaborate.
凝ってるね
hey.
ね
Having long legs.
足長いこと
Why, why is it so long?
なんで、なんでそんな長いの?
It's amazing even though I'm not wearing heels.
ヒール履いてないのにすごいじゃん
Really?
本当に?
Too cute.
かわいすぎる
Does it suit you?
似合ってるかな?
Looks great on you.
超似合ってる
She really is an idol now.
もうなんか、本当にアイドルだな
Because I took the brazier.
ブライジャー取ったからね
Is this okay?
これで いいかな?
It's super cute though.
超かわいいんですけど
Mejikai.
めじかい
That's crazy.
めじかいね
Let's tie your hair too.
髪の毛も結ぼう
It looks kind of cute when you wear it.
せっかく着たらちょっとかわいくね
I also want to take pictures.
写真とかも撮りたいから
I want to take pictures.
撮 りたい
Is this the neck?
これが首か
He looks better than this kid.
この子より似合ってるよ
This kid also looks a bit like an adult.
この子だってちょっと大人っぽいからさ
This girl is.
この女の子はさ
play
嬉
Yes.
しい
Yes, this is definitely a Noizaku.
はい、 もうこれはノイザク確定ですね
I can go.
いけますね
いける
Good.
よき
Good, good.
よ き よ き
cute.
かわいい
A child dressed like this, who is not cute,
こういう格好をした、かわいくない子が、
There are a lot of them standing on the streets of Akihabara.
秋葉原の路上にいっぱい立ってるもん
There's an uncute girl standing there.
かわいくない子が立ってる
There are a lot of uncute kids standing there.
かわいくない子いっぱい立ってるよ
If you're a popular girl, you're bound to get involved.
だ って人気な子はほら、手の入っちゃうでしょ
surely.
確 かに
They stand about 5 meters apart.
5メートル間隔くらいで立ってるよね
That's right, I'll just ask on social media.
そうだね、一応ソーシャルメッドで頼む
There are three.
3つです
Three, it's no good.
3つ、ダメだからね
What is this?
これ なんだ
これはなんだよ
It has a tail.
しっぽがついてんだ
Huh, cat ears?
え、猫耳?
It has a tail.
しっぽがついてる
I guess it's a cat.
一応猫なんだね
It's a cat maid.
猫メイドなんだね
It's good to wear it, after all.
はくといいね、やっぱ
The extra thinness of the legs is emphasized.
余計足の細さが強調
nice.
いいね
This foot...
この足...
Awesome.
すっごい
I like how short it is.
この短さがいいね
It's very short.
めっちゃ短い
Mi-chan.
み ーちゃん
Just give it a try.
ちょっと、ちょっとしてみて
Wow!
うわっ!
I think it's almost completed.
ほぼ完成かな
Also, you have hair, and you can put ears on it.
あと、じゃあ髪あって、それ、耳つけたらね
This is fine because the laces on the socks aren't cute.
これは ね、靴下のこのひもはかわいくないからいいや
Those two glasses are much better, and they are much better on their own.
その二杯のほうが全然、そのものが全然いいよ
Maybe I should just stand up.
ピッて立てればいいのかな
I was able to do it.
できた
Also, do you want to do your hair?
あと髪の毛やる?
That's right, with the hair, I guess I should try it once and then put it on.
そうだね、髪の毛じゃあ一回やってからそれつければいいのかな、
Also.
また
Do you need this?
これ要る?
You need that.
それ要るよね
Yeah, yeah.
かっ、うん
That's cool.
かっこいいね